Heavenly Sword is a adventure, action, animation film directed by Jang Gun-ho.
The film's plot follows that of the game closely.
Nariko, a member of an ancient tribe who have guarded an ancient magical sword for thousands of years, is charged
with bringing the sword to its destined wielder, a deity reincarnated who will bring peace to the land.
But on her quest, Nariko must wield the sword herself against the forces
of King Bohan, who wishes to possess the weapon himself.
Nariko (voice), played by Anna Torv.
King Bohan (voice), played by Alfred Molina.
Loki (voice), played by Thomas Jane.
Kai (voice), played by Ashleigh Ball.
Flying Fox / Prophet Takashi (voice), played by Barry Dennen.
Whiptail, Old Woman (voice), played by Renae Geerlings.
Heavenly Sword is a 2014 American adult animated action-adventure fantasy film based on the
2007 video game of the same name, developed by companies Sony and Ninja Theory.
It was released digitally, and theatrically in selected regions.